thecountrycaller.com 2016-05-11

# The Country Caller

TheCountryCaller places a high value on the privacy of its users. This Privacy Policy (“PP”) sets out the types of information that we may collect from users of [www.TheCountryCaller.com](http://www.morningtoday.com/) (the “Website”) and the purposes for which we may use such information. The PP and the Terms of Use (“TOU”) constitute a legally binding agreement between you and TheCountryCaller. If you do not agree to any part of the PP and/or TOU, you must not use the website. The PP may be modified from time to time and you are advised to check this page regularly.

**INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED**  
In addition to the other types of UGC that TheCountryCaller may collect from you and that may be used by it according to the licenses set forth in the TOU, TheCountryCaller may collect personally-identifiable information (called “personal information” in this PP) submitted to TheCountryCaller, including (but not limited to) information submitted when registering an account with us or filling out other forms.

This “personal information” may include (but not be limited to) your:  
Name  
Gender  
Date of birth  
Occupation  
Income range  
Home and/or work address  
Email address  
Telephone Numbers

TheCountryCaller may also periodically collect log files, including IP addresses, from our server. These files give a general picture of who is visiting the Website and which pages are being viewed most often.  
This information is collected to assist us in the maintenance and administration of the Website. Log files are collected mainly for research purposes to see what pages are of most interest and use to current and potential clients as well as to gather demographic, geographic and economic trends. TheCountryCaller reserves the right to make changes to this policy’s description of log files use at any time.

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
You hereby agree that TheCountryCaller may use your personal information for the following purposes:  
Administering the Website  
Personalizing the Website for you  
Sending you marketing communications, including on behalf of third party advertisers, provided such advertisers will not be provided access to your personally-identifiable information  
Sending you other electronic communications  
Enabling your access and use of the Website  
Monitoring compliance with the TOU  
Allowing you to use interactive features of the Website

**SECURITY**  
TheCountryCaller will exercise reasonable care, including taking technical and organisational precautions, in order to protect your personal data from unauthorized access or use. Your personal information will only be stored on secure servers owned, controlled or contracted for by TheCountryCaller. If TheCountryCaller contracts out its data hosting to a third party, we will endeavor to ensure that party has agreed to comply with our privacy standards as described in this PP.

Despite TheCountryCaller obligations to make reasonable efforts to protect personal information as set forth above, TheCountryCaller cannot provide perfect security, and will not be responsible or liable for damage, pecuniary or otherwise, caused by a third party’s unauthorized access to or use of your personal information. Further, TheCountryCaller shall not be responsible for maintaining or storing your personal information or other UGC for any particular period of time.

**DATA TRANSFER**  
Your personal information may be transferred internationally between the countries in which  
TheCountryCaller maintains a presence in order to enable the use of your data as specified in the PP.

**CHILD PRIVACY**  
TheCountryCaller considers the privacy of children to be especially important and prohibits children under the age of 16 from sending their personal information over the internet without their parent/guardian’s permission.

**THIRD PARTY SITES**  
The Website may contain links to third party sites. TheCountryCaller is not responsible for the practices of third parties and encourages users to read their privacy policies before using their websites.

**DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES**  
We do not share any of the personal information you provide to us with any third party other than service providers of ours who assist us in providing the information and/or services we are providing to you. To the extent that we do share your personal information with a service provider, we will endeavor to ensure that party has agreed to comply with our privacy standards as described in this PP.

**OTHER PERSONS’ PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
In using the Website, you may acquire access to others’ personal information, such as names and addresses. Your use of the Website constitutes your agreement to respect others’ privacy with respect to personal information. You may not, under any circumstances, release others’ personal information to third parties, including your employees who have no need for the information, without the written consent of both TheCountryCaller and the person or persons whose personal information you intend to forward. You may not, under any circumstances, use personal information obtained from the Website to send unsolicited email, facsimile transmissions, or spam, even if the person to whom you intend to send unsolicited email or spam has communicated with you in the past. You agree to immediately notify TheCountryCaller of any release or breach of any third party’s personal information (including name, address, phone numbers, email addresses, account numbers, investment histories, or social security number) that occurs as a result of use of the Website under your user name.
